cababstractsplus.org 2019-04-08

# Home | GeneTex

## Privacy Commitments

GeneTex takes your privacy very seriously. We have made our privacy policy easier to find and easier to read. We welcome your questions and feedback on our privacy policy, and invite you to contact us.

  * We will protect your privacy and keep your personal information safe. We use encryption and other security safeguards to protect customer data.
  * We will not sell your personal information to anyone, for any purpose.
  * We will fully disclose our privacy policy in plain language, and make our policy easily accessible to you.
  * We will notify you of revisions to our privacy policy, in advance.
  * We're listening. You can send us questions or feedback on our privacy policy.

## Privacy Policy Scope

This Privacy Policy identifies and describes the way GeneTex uses and protects the information we collect about Customers and Users.

## The Information We Collect, and How We Collect It

We may collect different types of personal and other information based on your use of our products and services and our business relationship with you. Some examples include:

  * Contact Information that allows us to communicate with you -- including your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address;
  * Billing information related to your financial relationship with us -- including your payment data, credit card number, security codes, and service history;
  * Website Usage, Viewing and other Technical Information about your use of our products, services or websites.

We collect information in two primary ways:

  * You give it to us when you purchase or interact with us about a product or service we offer or provide;
  * We collect it automatically when you visit our websites or use our products and services;

## We may use the information we collect in a variety of ways

GeneTex takes your privacy very seriously. We have made our privacy policy easier to find and easier to read. We welcome your questions and feedback on our privacy policy, and invite you to contact us.

  * Provide you with the best customer experience possible;
  * Provide the products and services you purchase, and to respond to your questions;
  * Communicate with you regarding product updates, offers, and promotions;
  * Deliver customized content and advertising that may be of interest to you;
  * Address network integrity and security issues.

## How GeneTex uses cookies

Cookies are very small text files saved to your computer that are used to track user navigation around a website. Cookies enable us to identify you or the device you are on when you have logged in.

We use cookies that are necessary to enable you to see certain features on our site. We also use cookies to help us improve the performance of our site providing you with a better user experience. This includes collecting standard information about visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the site and collect this information in a way which does not personally identify anyone.

We do not sell the information collected by cookies nor do we disclose information to third parties. When we want to collect personally identifiable information (for things like email sign ups), we will be explicit about this.

## How can I control or delete cookies

Most browsers allow you to manage your cookies settings. Check the following links for more information.
